A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), Laurance S. Rockefeller General Files, 1992-1996, RG 43 FA1325
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Education, 1992-1996; 13
  - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Human Potential Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
  - Institute for Philosophical and Social Research, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Institute for the Preservation of the Original Languages of the Americas, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Institute for 21st Century Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - International Center for Integrative Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Lindisfarne Association, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
  - Lindisfarne Association - Audiocassettes (2017:FA1325:002), 1992-1996; 6 audiocassettes (Box 2017:FA1325:002)
  - Millenium Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - National Geographic, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - National Geographic Society, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - National Humanities Center, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - National Institute of Social Sciences, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - New Dimensions Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Ojai Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Saybrook Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Snake River Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Wainwright House, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - The Waldorf Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Colleges - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1-7)
  - Colleges - Brown University, Providence, RI, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Colleges - California Institute of Integral Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Colleges - California Institute of Integral Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 23, Folder 1-11)
  - Colleges - California Institute of Integral Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - California Institute of Integral Studies 2017:FA1325:003 - Brian Swimme - Canticle to the Cosmos, 6 audiocassettes (Box 2017:FA1325:003)
  - Colleges - California Institute Integral Studies Center - Printed Matter, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Colleges - Cambridge College, Cambridge, MA, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Colleges - Center for Theology and Natural Sciences, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Colleges - City University of New York, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - Columbia University, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Colleges - Dartmouth College - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for Social Sciences, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Colleges - Dartmouth College, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Colleges - Duke University, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Colleges - Emory University, Atlanta, GA, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Colleges - Gordon - Conwell Theological Seminary, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Colleges - Harvard University - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - Harvard University - Center for the Study of World Religions, 1992-1996 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Colleges - Harvard University - Michael C. Rockefeller Memorial Scholarship, 1992-1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Colleges - Indiana University, Bloomington, IN, 1992-1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Colleges - Maharashi International University, 1992-1996 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - Maharashi International University - - 2017:FA1325:004 - A Proven Program to Reduce Crime and Enhance Governmental Effectiveness (Institute of Science, Technology and Public Policy), 1993; VHS, 17 minutes (Box 2017:FA1325:004)
  - Colleges - Marlboro Music, 1992-1996 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1992-1996 (Box 25, Folder 7-11)
  - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Contribution, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - The Naropa Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Colleges - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Colleges - Pacifica Graduate Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Colleges - Princeton University, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 6-10)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Alcohol Congress on Responsible Decisions, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Class of 1932, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 12-14)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Contributions, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Fundraising, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Fundraising - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Fundraising - Wu, Gordon Y. S., 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - LSR Dinner, 1994 May 4 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Louis Mars, Jr. '53 Hall, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Blairstown Center, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Princeton Theological Seminary, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Princeton Theological Seminary - 2017:FA1325:005 - Dr. James F. Kay - "On Trial for Hope", A Sermon at Miller Chapel, 1995 January 25; Audio (Box 2017:FA1325:005)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Printed Matter, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - School of Engineering-Applied Science, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 9-10)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - University Center for Human Values, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 11-14)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - University Center for Human Values - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - University Center for Human Values - Contributions, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - Spelman College, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 2-4)
  - Colleges - Stanford University, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - Stanford University - School of Medicine, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Colleges - State University of New York (SUNY), 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Colleges - State University of New York (SUNY) - Purchase College, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Colleges - State University of New York (SUNY)-Albany - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
  - Colleges - Union Theological Seminary, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Colleges - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Colleges - United Negro College Fund, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago, 1992-1996 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Divinity School, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - University of Hawaii, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Colleges - University of Louisville, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania Medical Center, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - University of Vermont, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Colleges - University of Wyoming, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Colleges - Vasser College, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Colleges - Vermont Law School, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Colleges - World College West, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Colleges - Yale University, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Education - Foreign Student Services - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Foundation - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 13-19)
  - Foundation - Asahi Glass Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Foundation - Elmer and Mamdouba Bobst Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Foundation - Joseph Campbell Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Foundation - Nathan Cummings Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Foundation - Northstar Fund, 1992-1996 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Foundation - Manitou Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 30, Folder 6-11)
  - Foundation - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Foundation - The Margaret Thatcher Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Foundation - Teewinot Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Foundation - Wallace Funds, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Foundation - Wallace Funds - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Foundation - DeWitt Wallace Reader's Digest Fund, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Foundation - DeWitt Wallace Reader's Digest Fund - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Foundation - DeWitt Wallace Reader's Digest Fund - Meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Foundation - DeWitt Wallace Reader's Digest Fund - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Foundation - Lila Wallace Reader's Digest Fund, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Foundation - Lila Wallace Reader's Digest Fund - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Foundation - Lila Wallace Reader's Digest Fund - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Foundation - Lila Wallace Reader's Digest Fund - Meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 1-5)
  - Historical Societies - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
  - Historical Societies - National Maritime Historical Societies, 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Historical Societies - White House Historical Association, 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Historical Societies - Woodstock Historical Society, 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Housing - International House, New York City, 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Radio-TV - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 12-14)
  - Radio-TV - Boleu, Jean Shinoda, 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Radio-TV - Educational Broadcasting Corporation, 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 2-3)
  - Radio-TV - Globalvision, 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Radio-TV - Globalvision - 2017:FA1325:006 - Judy Collins, "I Dream of Peace", Excerpted from Show 211, Children and Human Rights, "Rights and Wrongs: Human Rights Television", 1994; VHS (Box 2017:FA1325:006)
  - Radio-TV - Globalvision - 2017:FA1325:007 - Charlayne Hunter Gault - "Rights and Wrongs: Human Rights Television", 1993 November; VHS (Box 2017:FA1325:007)
  - Radio-TV - National Empowerment Television, 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Radio-TV - NET - Political Newstalk Network, 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
  - Radio-TV - NET - Political Newstalk Network - 2017:FA1325:008 - Changing the Picture, VHS, 9 minutes and 19 seconds (Box 2017:FA1325:008)
  - Radio-TV - WETA, 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Schools - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 1-5)
  - Schools - American Academy in Rome, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Schools - The Children's Storefront, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Schools - Diller - Quaile School of Music, New York, NY, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Schools - Manhattan Country School, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Schools - Miss Porter's School, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Schools - Outward Bound, USA, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Schools - St. John School of the Arts, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Schools - The School for Field Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Schools - The Sidwell Friends School, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Schools - Soundview Preparatory School, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Energy, 1992-1996; 14
  - Energy - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- F - General, 1992-1996; 15
  - F - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- G - General, 1992-1996; 16
  - G - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Geriatrics - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Greenacre Foundation - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Greenacre Foundation - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Greenacre Foundation - Minutes Meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 2-4)
- H - General, 1992-1996; 17
  - H - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Historic Hudson Valley, 1992-1996; 18
  - Historic Hudson Valley (HHV), 1988-1992 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Historic Hudson Valley (HHV) - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
  - Historic Hudson Valley (HHV) - Pomeroy, 1988-1992 (Box 35, Folder 9-10)
  - Annadale, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 12-15)
  - Contribution, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Development Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Pocantico Society, 1992-1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Clayton W. Frye - Rock and Co. Portfolio Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
  - Fundraising, 1992-1996 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
  - Fundraising - Clayton W. Frye file, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 8-9)
  - Fundraising, 1996 May 30 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising, 1995 June 8 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising - Phillipsburg Manor Tercentenary Celebration, 1993 June 12 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising - Playhouse Event, 1992 June 13 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Pocantico Survey - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising - Rainbow Room Events, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 16-17)
  - Fundraising - Rockefeller Archive Center Summer Dinner Dance, 1994 June 22 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Fundraising - Wallace, 1992-1996 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Greenways in the Hudson Valley, 1992-1996 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Kykuit, 1992-1996 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 37, Folder 2-10)
  - Personnel, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Personnel records.
  - Port Imperial Hudson River Cruises, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Printed Material, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - John D. Rockefeller Jr. Founder's Award, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Horticulture, 1992-1996; 19
  - Horticulture - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - New York Botanical Garden, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
- IBEC, 1992-1996; 20
  - IBEC, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- International Relations, 1992-1996; 21
  - International Relations - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
  - Asia - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Asian Cultural Council, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Asia Society - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Asia Society, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Asia Society - Contribution, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Asia - East-West Center Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - China - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - China - China Institute in America, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - France - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - France - French-American Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Gorbachev Foundation USA, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - International Rescue Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Kenya - Gallman Memorial Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Tibet - International Campaign for Tibet, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Aid - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Aid - CARE, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Aid - Resources Development Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Policy - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Policy - Foreign Policy Association, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 15-17)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - United Nations - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - United Nations - Association of the United States of America, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - United Nations - International Children's Emergency Fund, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - United Nations - Conference on Environment and Development, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Peace - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 3-4)
  - United States Government - Department of State - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- J - General, 1992-1996; 22
  - J - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- K - General, 1992-1996; 23
  - K - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- L - General, 1992-1996; 24
  - L - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- M - General, 1992-1996; 25
  - M - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - McCoy, Dr. Doris Lee, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Medicine, 1992-1996; 26
  - Medicine - A - O, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 11-17)
  - Medicine - P - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Alliance for Health Reform, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 3-6)
  - Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Association, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - American Cancer Society, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - American Foundation for AIDS Research, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - American Health Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Arthritis Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Botanical Dimensions, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Cancer Care, Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Cancer Research Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Circumcision Resource Center, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Deafness Research Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Fetzer Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 4-7)
  - Fetzer Institute - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - The Foundation for Mind Research, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Freedom Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - The Gerson Research Organization, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Health Commons Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - House Ear Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Development Training, 1992-1996 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Institute of Humanistic Society, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - International Center for Hearing and Speech Research, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation International, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Maharashi Ayur - Veda Association of America and Health Center, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Medical Illness Counseling Center, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
  - Mind-Body Medical Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - National Council on Alcoholism and Drug Dependence, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 8-9)
  - National Organization of Circumcision Information Resource Centers, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 10-11)
  - National Organization to Halt the Abuse and Routine Mutilation of Males (NOHARMM) - 2017:FA1325:009 - "Whose Body, Whose Rights" Video, 1996; VHS (Box 2017:FA1325:009)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - New York Blood Center, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Omega Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Pew Health Professions Commissions, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Salk Institute for Biological Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Shaman Pharmaceuticals, Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Sharp Healthcare and Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - VZV Research Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Voice Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Alcoholism - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Alcoholism - Children of Alcoholics Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 11-12)
  - Alcoholism - The Weekend Center, 1992-1996 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Hospitals - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - Hospitals - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Hospitals - Dartmouth-Hotchcock Medical Center, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Hospitals - Dartmouth-Hotchcock Medical Center - Audubon Prints, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Hospitals - Eisenhower Medical Center, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Hospitals - Hospital for Special Surgery, New York, NY, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Hospitals - The Marshfield Clinic, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 45, Folder 10-12)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Annual Reports, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Annual Reports, 1992-1995 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1992-1996 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - By-Laws, 1978-1996 (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Breifing Book for New Members of the Board of Overseers, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Board of Managers and Overseers, 1992-1996 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Contributions, 1992-1996 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Convocation, 1992-1996 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Jackson Hole, Wyoming Meeting - Development Program Review, 1994 August (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Fundraising, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Fundraising - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 3-4)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Fundraising - DeWitt Wallace Fund, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Caryl Hall Studios, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Health Care Reform, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Joint Nominating Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - McCrary, Tex (John Reagan), 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Meetings - Board of Managers, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Meetings - Board of Overseers and Board of Managers, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Meetings - Institutional Policy Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Memorial Hospital, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - 1995 Annual Report (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Oral History, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - The President's Council, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Printed Material, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Research and Educational Programs, 1993-1995 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Rockefeller Research Laboratories, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Russian Cancer Program, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Staff - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Society of MSKCC - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Society of MSKCC - Fundraising - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Society of MSKCC - History, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Thomas, Dr. Lewis, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Hospitals - Mount Sinai Medical Center, New York, NY, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 13-14)
  - Hospitals - North Hawaii Community Hospital, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Hospitals - Phelps Memorial Hospital Center, North Tarrytown, NY, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 16)